A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.39 (A2014) FA760
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2014.012: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 2006-2014; AC_2014_012; 27.99 Cubic Feet 21 standard record storage boxes, R4413-4433, 1 letter document box and 1 clamshell box
  - EIN, 2010-2013; AC_2014_012_15; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage boxes
    - 2011 EIN 302 - SOCIAL FINANCE - SOCIAL IMPACT BOND INSTRUMENT, 2011-2013 (Box R4420)
    - 2011 EIN 303 - SEACHANGE CAPTIAL PARTNERS - SOCIAL IMPACT BOND INTERMEDIARY, 2011-2012 (Box R4420)
    - 2011 EIN 307 - TEACHERS COLLEGE, COLUMBIA COLLEGE - TOOLKIT ON INNOVATION METHODS, 2011-2013 (Box R4420)
    - 2011 EIN 308 - UNIVERSITY OF WATERLOO (CANADA) - INNOVATION FOR RESILIENCE FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM, 2011-2013 (Box R4420)
    - 2011 EIN 309 - NONPROFIT FINANCE FUND - STUDY ON SOCIAL IMPACT BOND INSTRUMENT, 2010-2012 (Box R4420)
    - 2011 EIN 310 - POPTECH INSTITUTE - CLIMATE RESILIENCE AND VULNERABLE POPULATIONS, 2011-2013 (Box R4420)
    - 2011 EIN 311 - CHILDREN'S AID SOCIETY - SOCIAL IMPACT BOND DEVELOPMENT, 2011-2013 (Box R4420)
    - 2011 EIN 312 - CENTER FOR AMERICAN PROGRESS - BIPARTISAN DIALOGUE ON SOCIAL IMPACT BONDS, 2011-2013 (Box R4420)
    - 2011 EIN 314 - RESTAURANT OPPORTUNITIES CENTERS UNITED - INNOVATION AWARD, 2011-2013 (Box R4420)
  - EVA, 2010-2013; AC_2014_012_16; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 EVA 301 - PACT INSTITUTE - ADVANCING NEW INNOVATIVE METHODS AND PRACTICE IN IMPACT EVALUATION, 2011-2013 (Box R4420)
    - 2011 EVA 303 - UNIVERSITY OF THE FREE STATE (SOUTH AFRICA) - EVALUATION AND IMPACT SPECIALISTS TO TRAIN RF AND DEVELOPMENT COMMUNITY, 2010-2013 (Box R4420)
  - Innovation (INN), 2007-2012; AC_2014_012_17; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2011 INN 301 - TIDES CENTER - EVALUATION OF INNOVATION FOR DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVE, 2011-2012 (Box R4420)
    - 2011 INN 302 - ETC FOUNDATION (NETHERLANDS) - FARMER ACCESS TO INNOVATION RESOURCES (2 FOLDERS), 2007-2012 (Box R4420)
    - 2011 INN 302 - ETC FOUNDATION (NETHERLANDS) - FARMER ACCESS TO INNOVATION RESOURCES (2 FOLDERS), 2007-2012 (Box R4421)
  - INV, 2009-2013; AC_2014_012_18; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 INV 302 - GLOBAL ALLIANCE FOR BANKING ON VALUES (NETHERLANDS) - IMPACT OF VALUES - BASED BANKS, 2011-2012 (Box R4421)
    - 2011 INV 303 - IC FOUNDATION -GENERAL SUPPORT, 2011-2012 (Box R4421)
    - 2011 INV 306 - NEW VENTURE FUND - OPEN SOURCE DISSEMINATION OF BEST PRACTICES, 2011-2013 (Box R4421)
    - 2011 INV 307 - MARS DISCOVERY DISTRICT (CANADA) - CENTRE FOR IMPACT INVESTING, 2011-2013 (Box R4421)
    - 2011 INV 311 - INTELLEVENTURES LLC DBA KINETICS CONSULTING SERVICES - POLICY RESEARCH TO DEVELOP IMPACT INVESTING IN INDIA, 2011-2013 (Box R4421)
    - 2011 INV 312 - EDWARD T. JACKSON AND ASSOCIATES (CANADA) - IMPACT INVESTING EVALUATION, 2011-2013 (Box R4421)
    - 2011 INV 313 - CALVERT FOUNDATION - STRATEGIC PLANNING SUPPORT, 2011-2012 (Box R4421)
    - 2011 INV 314 - GIIRS - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2009-2013 (Box R4421)
    - 2011 INV 316 - GODEKE CONSULTING - SOCIAL IMPACT BONDS MARKET RESEARCH, 2011-2013 (Box R4421)
  - OAF, 2010-2013; AC_2014_012_19; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2011 OAF 302 - SOCIETY FOR INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT EAST AFRICA (KENYA) - AFRICAN DIALOGUE SPEAKER SERIES, 2011-2013 (Box R4421)
    - 2011 OAF 303 - NELSON MANDELA CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL TRUST (SOUTH AFRICA) - CORPORATE SOCIAL RESPONSIBILITIES, INNOVATIVE PUBLIC PRIVATE PARNTERSHIP HOSPITAL FINANCING MODEL, 2011-2013 (Box R4421)
    - 2011 OAF 304 - AFRICAN TECHNOLOGY POLICY STUDIES NETWORK (KENYA) - WORKSHOP ON POLICY RESEARCH AND POLICYMAKING FOR AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT, 2010-2012 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OAF 305 - AFRICA HEALTH AND DEVELOPMENT INTERNATIONAL (KENYA) - DOCUMENTARY SERIES, PRESERVATION OF AFRIAN CULTURE AND KNOWLEDGE, 2011-2013 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OAF 306 - WILDLIFE CONSERVATION SOCIETY - ONE HEALTH LEADERSHIP IN AFRICA, 2011-2013 (Box R4422)
  - OAS, 2011-2013; AC_2014_012_21; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 OAS 301 - UNITED NATIONS ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COMMISSION FOR ASIA AND THE PACIFIC (THAILAND) - FIFTH ASIA-PACIFIC URBAN FORUM, 2011-2012 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OAS 302 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - TAGORE EXHIBITION AND SEMINAR, 2011-2012 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OAS 303 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY - IPSR ANNUAL CONFERENCES 2011, 2012, 2011-2013 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OAS 305 - PATTANARAK FOUNDATION (THAILAND) - CAPACITY BUILDING FOR FOOD PRODUCTION ALONG THAI-BURMA BORDER, 2011-2013 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OAS 306 - VIETNAM MUSEUM OF ETHNOLOGY, VIETNAMESE ACADEMY FOR SOCIAL SCIENCES - CONFERENCE ON CLIMATE CHANGE AWARENESS, 2011-2012 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OAS 309 - TARU LEADING EDGE PRIVATE LIMITED (INDIA) - EXPLORATORY STUDY ON CREATING SAFE WET MARKETS, 2011-2012 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OAS 310 - MIRROR FOUNDATION (THAILAND) - STRENGTHENING COMMUNITY DISASTER, 2011-2012 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OAS 313 - INTERNATIONAL HEALTH POLICY PROGRAM (THAILAND) - CONFERENCE ON ALCOHOL - HEALTH AND PREVENETION, 2011-2012 (Box R4422)
  - OPP, 2010-2013; AC_2014_012_22; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2011 OPP 303 - CITY FUTURES - DESIGNING NEW YORK'S INNOVATION ECONOMY, 2011-2012 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OPP 304 - PRATT INSTITUTE - BROOKLYN NAVY YARD ECONOMIC IMPACT STUDY, 2010-2012 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OPP 306 - MAKE THE ROAD TO NEW YORK - WORKPLACE JUSTICE PROJECT, 2011-2013 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OPP 310 - PRATT INSTITUTE - GREEN SCHOOLS AND GREEN ECONOMY, 2011-2012 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OPP 312 - CREATIVE TIME, INC. - ARTISTS ON THE NEWS, 2011-2012 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OPP 313 - MUNICIPAL ART SOCIETY OF NEW YORK - SURVEY, SUMMIT FOR NEW YORK CITY, 2010-2012 (Box R4422)
    - 2011 OPP 314 - COMMON GROUND COMMUNITIES - BROWNSVILLE PARTNERSHIP, 2011-2013 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 OPP 316 - NEW MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY ART - HUB RESIDENCY PROGRAM FOR INTERNATIONAL ARTISTS, 2011-2013 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 OPP 317 - LOWER MANHATTAN CULTURAL COUNCIL - INSITE - ART SEPTEMBER 11th COMMEMORATION, 2011-2012 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 OPP 318 - VERA INSTITUTE OF JUSTICE - STOP AND FRISK IMPACT STUDY, 2011-2013 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 OPP 321 - NATURAL RESOURCES DEFENSE COUCIL - GREEN RETROFIT MARKET, 2011-2013 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 OPP 323 - CENTER FOR AMERICAN PROGRESS - OCCUPY WALL STREET-INSPIRED POLICY PROJECT, 2011-2012 (Box R4423)
  - PHS, 2007-2013; AC_2014_012_23; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 PHS 301 - WORLD AFFAIRS COUNCIL ON NORTHERN CALIFORNIA - 2011 GLOBAL PHILANTRHOPY FORUM, 2011-2012 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 PHS 308 - URBAN INSTITUTE - OUTCOMES AND EFFECTIVE PRACTICES PORTAL, 2011-2012 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 PHS 310 - COMPUMENTOR PROJECT - NGO REPOSITORY, 2009-2012 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 PHS 313 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION PHILANTRHOPIC SECTOR CONTRIBUTIONS - "SHORT-FORM" CONTRIBUTIONS, 2007-2011 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 PHS 316 - KENYA COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT FOUNDATION - AFRICAN PHILANTHROPY, 2011-2013 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 PHS 317 - FOUNDATION FOR THAILAND RURAL RECONSTRUCTION MOVEMENT UNDER ROYAL PATRONAGE - SOCIAL INVESTMENT PLATFORM, 2012-2013 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 PHS 319 - INDEPENDENT SECOR - IS NETWORK AND BUSINESS MODEL, 2011-2013 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 PHS 320 - CLINTON GLOBAL INITIATIVE - 2011 ANNUAL CONFERENCE (Box R4423)
  - PRD, 2011-2013; AC_2014_012_24; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2011 PRD 201 - MONITOR COMPANY GROUP LP - JOBS AND ECONOMIC GROWTH IN SOUTH AFRICA, KENYA AND GHANA LANDSCAPE ANALYSIS, 2011-2012 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 PRD 202 - TECHNOSERVE - IMPACT SOURCING IN RURAL AND URBAN KENYA, 2011-2013 (Box R4423)
    - 2001 PRD 203 - ENABLIS ENTREPRENEURIAL NETWORK EAST AFRICA LIMITED - ENABLIS ROCKEFELLER IMPACT SOURCING PROJECT, 2011-2013 (Box R4423)
    - 2011 PRD 204 - AVASANT - INCENTIVES OPPORTUNITIES FOR IMPACT SOURCING, 2011-2012 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRD 207 - COMMUNITY AND INDIVIDUAL DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATION (SOUTH AFRICA) - SA DEMONSTRATIONS, 2011-2012 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRD 208 - KENYA INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATIONS TECHNOLOGY BOARD - DIGITIZE GOVERNMENT RECORDS, KENYATTA HOSPITAL, 2011-2012 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRD 210 - LEADERS' QUEST, LTD. (UNITED KINGDOM) - IMPACT SOURCING LEARNING, 2011-2012 (Box R4424)
  - PRE, 2011-2013; AC_2014_012_25; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 PRE 301 - LOCAL INITIATIVES SUPPORT COOPERATION - IMPORTANCE OF COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT AWARENESS (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRE 302 - EARTH ISLAND INSTITUTE - CLIMATE WISE WOMEN PROJECT, 2011-2012 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRE 303 - CORPORATION FOR NATIONAL AND COMMUNITY SERVICE - COMMUNITY YOUTH ENGAGEMENT PROGRAMS, 2011-2013 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRE 304 - BROWN UNIVERSITY - INDIGENOUS AFRICAN IGBO LANGUAGE, 2011-2012 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRE 305 - ROCKEFELLER PHILANTRHOPY ADVISORS - WOMEN IN THE WORLD FOUNDATION, 2011-2012 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRE 306 - CLUB OF MADRID FOUNDATION - CONFERENCE ON DIGITAL TECHNOLOGIES FOR DEMOCRACY IN THE 21ST CENTURY, 2011-2012 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRE 307 - HABITAT FOR HUMANITY INTERNATIONAL - WORLD HABITAT DAY, 2011-2012 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRE 308 - INTERNATIONAL WOMEN'S MEDIA FOUNDATION - 2011 COURAGE IN JOURNALISM AWARDS, 2011-2012 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRE 309 - WASHINGTON DC MARTIN LUTHER KING JR NATIONAL MEMORIAL PROJECT FOUNDATION - MLK MEMORIAL, 2011-2012 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRE 310 - JAZZ AT LINCOLN CENTER - 2011-2012 NEW PROGRAM (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRE 311 - MIAMI CITY BALLET - PRESENTATION OF SAINT-LEON'S COPPELIA, 2011-2012 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 PRE 312 - CARNEGIE HALL SOCIETY - NATIONAL YOUTH ORCHESTRA USA, 2011-2013 (Box R4424)
  - RES, 2009-2013; AC_2014_012_26; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2011 RES 301 - MILLENNIUM PROJECT CORPORATION - MEMBERSHIP FEE AND SUPPORT FOR GLOBAL SOUTH PARTICIPATION, 2010-2012 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 RES 305 - CENTER FOR DEMOCRACY AND DEVELOPMENT (NIGERIA) - TREND MONITORING AND HORIZON SCANNING IN WEST AFRICA, 2009-2013 (Box R4424)
    - 2011 RES 306 - INTELLECAP INC. - POVERTY AND HUMAN DEVELOPMENT IN INDIA, BANGLADESH AND PAKISTAN (1 and 1 SUPPL), 2009-2013 (Box R4425)
    - 2011 RES 307 - NOVISCAPE CONSULTING GROUP CO. LTD. (THAILAND) - TREND MONITORING AND HORIZON SCANNING IN SOUTHEAST ASIA, 2009-2012 (Box R4425)
    - 2011 RES 308 - INSTITUTE FOR ALTERNATIVE FUTURES - ORGANIZATION OF ANNUAL SEARCHLIGHT, 2011-2012 (Box R4425)
  - SEG, 2008-2013; AC_2014_012_27; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2011 SEG 201 - INNOVATION NETWORK FOR COMMUNITIES - BETTER BUILDINGS PROGRAM, 2010-2012 (Box R4425)
    - 2011 SEG 202 - THE DC PROJECT - NATIONAL TRAINING PROGRAM, 2011-2012 (Box R4425)
    - 2011 SEG 203 - PROGRESSIVE AMERICA FUND - GREEN JOBS/GREEN HOMES IN NEW YORK, 2008-2012 (Box R4425)
    - 2011 SEG 204 - GREEN FOR ALL - WATER MANAGEMENT AND INFRASTRUCTURE, 2011-2013 (Box R4425)
    - 2011 SEG 205 - CAPITAL E LLC - GREEN BUILDING PERFORMANCE DATABASE, 2011-2013 (Box R4425)
    - 2011 SEG 206 - INSTITUTE FOR WOMEN'S POLICY RESEARCH - GENDER ANALYSIS OF GREEN JOBS, 2011-2013 (Box R4425)
    - 2011 SEG 208 - PACIFIC INSTITUTE - WATER RESEARCH, 2011-2013 (Box R4425)
    - 2011 SEG 209 - MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - EVALUTATION OF MICHIGAN WEATHERIZATION ASSISTANCE PROGRAM, 2011-2013 (Box R4425)
    - 2011 SEG 210 - UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN-MADISON - GREENER ON RAMPS RESEARCH, 2011-2012 (Box R4426)
    - 2011 SEG 211 - CLEAN ECONOMY DEVELOPMENT CENTER - STATE-WIDE ENERGY EFFICIENCY PROGRAM IN RHODE ISLAND, 2011-2013 (Box R4426)
    - 2011 SEG 212 - WORKERS DEFENSE PROJECT - GREEN BUILDING RATING SYSTEM, 2011-2013 (Box R4426)
    - 2011 SEG 213 - PARTNERSHIP FOR WORKING FAMILIES - RESEARCH ON WASTE MANAGEMENT CAMPAIGN, 2011-2013 (Box R4426)
    - 2011 SEG 214 - CLEAN ENERGY WORKS OREGON - RESIDENTIAL ENERGY RETROFIT PROGRAM, 2011-2013 (Box R4426)
    - 2011 SEG 215 - CNT ENERGY - REPLICATE ENERGY SAVER MODEL IN NEW MARKETS, 2011-2013 (Box R4426)
    - 2011 SEG 216 - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF LA RAZA - LATINOS AND GREEN JOBS, 2011-2013 (Box R4426)
    - 2011 SEG 218 - ECONOMIC POLICY INSTITUTE - GREEN JOBS LABOR MARKET RESEARCH, 2011-2013 (Box R4426)
    - 2011 SEG 219 - BLUEGREEN ALLIANCE FOUNDATION - GREEN MANUFACTURING CENTER, 2009-2012 (Box R4426)
  - SPE, 2011-2012; AC_2014_012_28; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 SPE 207 - ENERGY AND RESOURCES INSTITUTE (INDIA) - DELHI SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT SUMMIT, 2011-2012 (Box R4426)
  - Search (SRC), 2008-2014; AC_2014_012_29; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - 2011 SRC 101 - PACIFIC INSTITUTE - WATER SERVICE DELIVERY IN THE GLOBAL SOUTH, 2011-2012 (Box R4426)
    - 2011 SRC 102 - WINROCK INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT - MULTIPLE USE WATER SYSTEMS MODELS, 2011-2012 (Box R4426)
    - 2011 SRC 103 - CITY FUTURES - DOMESTIC URBAN COUNCIL'S MEETING (Box R4426)
    - 2011 SRC 104 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - BC CONFERENCE - ACCELERATING MULTIPLE WATER SERVICES FOR THE POOR, 2011-2012 (Box R4426)
    - 2011 SRC 105 - OPENPLANS - URBAN SYSTEMS SYMPOSIUM, New York City, 2011-2012 (Box R4227)
    - 2011 SRC 106 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA AT CHAPEL HILL - PREEMPTING OBESITY EPIDEMIC IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2011-2012 (Box R4227)
    - 2011 SRC 109 - ACCENTURE LLP - GENERATING IDEAS FOR SEARCH, 2011-2013 (Box R4227)
    - 2011 SRC 112 - NETHOPE - GENERATING IDEAS FOR SEARCH, 2011-2012 (Box R4227)
    - 2011 SRC 114 - INTERNATIONAL WATER MANAGEMENT INSTITUTE - AFRICA AND SOUTH ASIA RESEARCH MULTIPLE USE WATER SERVICES, 2011-2012 (Box R4227)
    - 2011 SRC 115 - JANOT MENDLER DE SUAREZ - RESILIENCE CONVENING AND RESILIENCE GAME DEVELOPMENT (Box R4227)
    - 2011 SRC 116 - ASIAN COALITION FOR HOUSING RIGHTS (THAILAND) - COMMUNITY-DRIVEN PROJECTS IN POOR URBAN AREAS IN ASIA, 2008-2013 (Box R4227)
    - 2011 SRC 117 - GUJARAT MAHILA HOUSING SEWA TRUST (INDIA) - HOUSING FINANCE FACILITY, 2011-2013 (Box R4227)
    - 2011 SRC 118 - IDEO.ORG-GENERATING IDEAS FOR SEARCH, 2011-2014 (Box R4227)
    - 2011 SRC 119 - WORLD BANK - DEFINING GENDER IN THE XXI CENTURY BELLAGIO CONFERENCE, 2011-2013 (Box R4227)
    - 2011 SRC 120 - BRAZILIAN FOUNDATION FOR SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT - JOINT INITIATIVE ON URBAN SUSTAINABILITY, 2011-2012 (Box R4227)
    - 2011 SRC 121 - MUUNGANO SUPPORT TRUST (KENYA) - DWELLERS IN KENYA MUNICIPALITIES, 2011-2013 (Box R4227)
    - 2011 SRC 122 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - CREATE EVENT DONATIONS (Box R4227)
    - 2011 SRC 123 - WORLD RESOURCES INSTITUTE - EMBARQ CENTER FOR SUSTAINABLE TRANSPORTATION, 2011-2013 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 125 - UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN - SUSTAINABLE MOBILITY, ACCESSIBILITY RESEARCH AND TRANSFORMATION, 2011-2013 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 129 - POPTECH INSTITUTE - POPTECH 2012 - TOWARD RESILIENCE, 2011-2012 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 130 - MERIDIAN INSTITUTE - DISASTER RISK REDUCTION IN ASIA PACIFIC REGION, 2011-2012 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 131 - NATIONAL COUNCIL FOR SCIENCE AND THE ENVIRONMENT - ENVIRONMENT AND SECURITY CONFERENCE, 2011-2012 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 134 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - SOVEREIGN WEALTH FUNDS, 2011-2012 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 135 - JEWISH FUNDS FOR JUSTICE - CARING ACROSS GENERATIONS CAMPAIGN, 2011-2012 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 138 - GREATER WASHINGTON EDUCATIONAL TELECOMMUNICATIONS ASSOCIATION - COPING WITH CLIMATE CHANGE, 2011-2013 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 138 - PBS News Hour Climate Change Series - Digital Material, 2011-2013; 2014:012:064, 2014:012:065 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 140 - NATURAL RESOURCES DEFENSE COUNCIL - MAJOR BUYERS INITIATIVE TO ADVANCE SUSTAINABILITY IN THE FOOD SYSTEM, 2011-2012 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 141 - BLUEGREEN ALLIANCE FOUNDATION-CERTIFICATION STANDARDS FOR NICHE FOOD MARKET, 2011-2012 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 142 - ECONOMIC MOBILITY CORP - EVALUATION OF ARRA PROGRAM, 2011-2013 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 143 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - PUBLIC-PRIVATE PARTNERSHIPS IN U.S. INFRASTRUCTURE FINANCE, 2011-2013 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 144 - TELLUS INSTITUTE - RESEARCH ON CORPORATE INITIATVES FOR JOB QUALITY AND EQUITY IN FOOD DISTRIBUTION, 2011-2012 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 145 - UNIVERSITY OF THE FREE STATE (SOUTH AFRICA) - DEFINING EQUITABLE GROWTH, 2011-2012 (Box R4428)
    - 2011 SRC 147 - WILLIAM DAVIDSON INSTITUTE - LANDSCAPING RESEARCH OF IMPACT ENTERPRISES, 2011-2013 (Box R4429)
    - 2011 SRC 149 - RSF SOCIAL FINANCE - FIINANCING MODELS FOR FOOD SYSTEMS, 2011-2012 (Box R4429)
    - 2011 SRC 150 - APPLIED RESEARCH CENTER - FOOD JUSTICE ISSUES, 2011-2012 (Box R4429)
    - 2011 SRC 151 - MDRC - RANDOM ASSIGNMENT EVALUATION OF TRANSITIONAL EMPLOYMENT PROGRAMS, 2011-2012 (Box R4429)
- AC.2014.057: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1999-2014; AC_2014_057; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R4434-R4436
  - Special Programs (SP), 1999-2007; AC_2014_057_1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 1999 SP 401 - PIONEER SOCIAL VENTURES - PRI - EMPLOYEMENT OPPORTUNITIES PROGRAMS, 1999-2002 (Box R4434)
    - 2001 SP 402 - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION - PRI - GLOBAL SOUND PROJECT, 2000-2007 (Box R4434)
  - Global Philanthropy (GP), 2000-2007; AC_2014_057_2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 GP 008 - AGA KHAN FOUNDATION U.S.A. - PHILANTHROPY IN ASIA AND AFRICA, 2000-2007 (Box R4434)
  - Assets and Capacities (AC), 2001-2014; AC_2014_057_3; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2002 AC 403 - ORIGIN, INC. - PRI - WELFARE RECIPIENTS AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY JOBS (2 FOLDERS), 2001-2005 (Box R4434)
    - 2003 AC 400 - (ASSETS CAPACITIES - PROVENEX) - AFRICAN AGRICULTURAL CAPITAL, 2003-2005 (Box R4434)
    - 2003 AC 401 - (ASSETS CAPACITIES - PROVENEX) - SOCIAL RETURN ON INVESTMENT PROJECT, 2002-2005 (Box R4435)
    - 2003 AC 402 - JACOBS CENTER FOR NEIGHBORHOOD INNOVATION - PRI - MARKET CREEK PLAZA (2 FOLDERS), 2003-2014 (Box R4435)
    - Story of Kindness - Digital Material, 2003-2014; 2014:057:003 (Box R4435)
    - To Be Made Over Tales of Socialist Reeducation in Vietnam - Published Material, 2003-2014; 2014:057:004 (Box R4435)
    - Vietnamese Poetry From The Wars - Published Material, 2003-2014; 2014:057:005 (Box R4435)
    - Writing Between The Lines - Published Material, 2003-2014; 2014:057:006 (Box R4435)
    - Surviving Twice Amerasian Children of the Vietnam War - Published Material, 2003-2014; 2014:057:007 (Box R4435)
    - Surviving Twice Ameriasian Children of the Vietnam War - Published Material, 2003-2014; 2014:057:008 (Box R4435)
    - Poems From Early Vietnam - Published Material, 2003-2014; 2014:057:009 (Box R4435)
    - 2004 AC 402 - (ASSETS AND CAPACITIES - PROVENEX) - WORKSHOP, "BUILDING THE BLENDED VALUE CAPITAL MARKET", 2004-2005 (Box R4436)
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), 2008-2010; AC_2014_057_4; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2003 CC 039 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS - RESIDENT FELLOWS (WILLIAM JOINER CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF WAR AND SOCIAL CONSEQUENCES) (1 and 2 Suppl), 2008-2010 (Box R4435, Box R4436)
    - 2003 CC 039 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS - RESIDENT FELLOWS (WILLIAM JOINER CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF WAR AND SOCIAL CONSEQUENCES) (1 and 2 Suppl), 2008-2010 (Box R4435, Box R4436)
  - Food Security (FS), 2005-2013; AC_2014_057_5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2005 FS 045 - MOZAMBIQUE - MINISTRY OF AGRICULTURE AND RURAL DEVELOPMENT - DISTRICT-LEVEL MARKET INFORMATION SYSTEMS, 2005-2013 (Box R4436)
  - SE, 2005-2014; AC_2014_057_6; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2007 SE 013 - MIRROR FOUNDATION (THAILAND) - VIRTUAL HILLTRIBE MUSEUM PROJECT, 2005-2014 (Box R4436)
    - 2007 SOL 303 - ALLIANCE FOR A GREEN REVOLUTION IN AFRICA - LARGE SCALE ADOPTION OF IMPROVED SOIL FERTILITY MANAGEMENT PRACTICES, 2008-2012 (Box R4436)
  - CAB, 2008-2014; AC_2014_057_7; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2008 CAB 307 - UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN (SOUTH AFRICA) - USHEPiA PROGRAM, 2008-2014 (Box R4436)
    - 2008 CAB 309 - FORUM FOR AFRICAN WOMEN EDUCATIONALISTS (KENYA) - WOMEN IN HIGHER EDUCATION, 2008-2013 (Box R4436)
    - 2008 CAB 310 - SOUTH AFRICAN INSTITUTE FOR DISTANCE EDUCATION - PHEA EDUCATIONAL TECHNOLOGY INITIATIVE, 2008-2013 (Box R4436)
    - 2008 CAB 311 - NIGERIA ICT FORUM - BANDWIDTH CONSORTIUM, 2008-2012 (Box R4436)
  - DSN, 2008-2014; AC_2014_057_8; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2008 DSN 302 - RAND CORPORATION - STRENGTHENING MBDS CAPACITY IN POLICY RESEARCH AND MONITORING EVALUATION, 2008-2014 (Box R4436)
    - 2008 DSN 310 - SOKOINE UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURE (TANZANIA) - INFECTIOUS DISEASES PREPAREDNESS, 2008-2013 (Box R4436)
    - The Ethnic Group in Thailand - Published Material, 2008-2013; 2014:057:001 (Box R4436)
    - The Ethnic Group in Thailand - Digital Material, 2008-2013; 2014:057:002 (Box R4436)
- AC.2014.068: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2014; AC_2014_068; 8.72 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, R4437-R4442, and one large flat file
  - New Orleans (NOL), 2008-2013; AC_2014_068_1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2008 NOL 306 - ENTERPRISE COMMUNITY PARTNERS - NEW ORLEANS COMMUNITY REDEVELOPMENT AND CAPACITY BUILDING, 2008-2013 (Box R4437)
  - Search (SRC), 2008-2014; AC_2014_068_2; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2008 SRC 114 - UNIVERSITY OF SUSSEX (ENGLAND) - IMPACT OF MIGRATION ON YOUTH, 2008-2013 (Box R4437)
    - 2009 SRC 107 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - URBAN HEALTH, PLANNING AND FINANCE LANDSCAPING IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2008-2014 (Box R4437)
    - 2009 SRC 107 - Suggested Readings Changing Cities - Digital, 2008-2014; 2014:068:002 (Box R4437)
    - 2009 SRC 107 - Women's Health and the World's Cities - Published Material, 2008-2014; 2014:068:003 (Box R4437)
    - 2009 SRC 107 - The Penn Resolution: Educating Urban Designers for Post-Carbon Cities - Published Material, 2008-2014; 2014:068:004 (Box R4437)
    - 2009 SRC 107 - Global Urbanization - Published Material, 2008-2014; 2014:068:005 (Box R4437)
    - Changing Cities - Linking Global Knowledge to Local Action - Published Material, 2008-2014; 2014:068:006 (Box R4437)
    - 2009 SRC 109 - MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - GRADUATE CURRICULUM IN URBAN PLANNING TO HELP CITIES IN INDIA (1 and 1 Suppl Folder), 2008-2013 (Box R4437, Box R4438)
    - 2009 SRC 109 - Towards a Global Learning Community - Published Material, 2008-2013; 2014:068:007 (Box R4438)
    - 2009 SRC 149 - UNIVERSITY COLLEGE LONDON, UNIVERSITY OF LONDON (ENGLAND) - GRADUATE CURRICULUM IN URBAN PLANNING, 2009-2013 (Box R4438)
    - 2010 SRC 115 - GREATER WASHINGTON EDUCATIONAL TELECOMMUNICATIONS ASSOCIATION - THE LATINO AMERICANS INITIATIVE, 2010-2014 (Box R4439)
    - 2010 SRC 115 - Latino Americans - Digital, 2010-2014; 2014:068:011-2014:068:013 (Box R4439)
    - 2010 SRC 116 - SYRACUSE UNIVERSITY - BOOK SERIES, NEW CITY BOOKS, 2010-2014 (Box R4439)
    - 2010 SRC 116 - New City Books Modern American Housing - Published Material, 2010-2014; 2014:068:014 (Box R4439)
    - 2010 SRC 116 - New City Books New Public Works - Published Material, 2010-2014; 2014:068:015 (Box R4439)
    - 2010 SRC 116 - New City Books American City "X"- Published Material, 2010-2014; 2014:068:016 (Box R4439)
    - 2010 SRC 116 - New City Books From the Ground Up - Published Material, 2010-2014; 2014:068:017 (Box R4439)
    - 2010 SRC 116 - New City Books Formerly Urban - Published Material, 2010-2014; 2014:068:018 (Box R4439)
    - 2010 SRC 144 - SHACK DWELLERS INTERNATIONAL (SOUTH AFRICA) - SHELTER STRATEGIES FOR CITIES, 2010-2014 (Box R4439)
  - CIF, 2008-2014; AC_2014_068_3; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2009 CIF 306 - BRIC ARTS/MEDIA/BKLYN - PROBABLE FIREWORKS/CROSSING BORDERS PROGRAM, 2009-2014 (Box R4437)
    - 2009 CIF 316 - PROJECT ENTERPRISE - ARTIST PEER LOAN PROGRAM, 2009-2014 (Box R4437)